Casper Leerink

Vancouver, BC V5K 2S2 casperleerink@gmail.com 6048389941

Hi, thank you for reading my resume!

My name is Casper, I grew up in the Netherlands where I finished my bachelors degree. For my masters degree I moved to Vancouver, where I am currently living.

My interests are a cross-section between art, technology and education. Over the years I have gained experience in all three directions. I have developed my artistic side finishing a bachelors degree in classical piano performance as well as a masters in Interdisciplinary Studies.

During this time, because of my interest in electronic music, I gained experience in programming for both music software, micro controllers as well as websites. I became proficient with these technologies, mostly by practising them in my own projects as well as with the help of online tutorials and courses. As a Digital Media Facilitator at the maker space of Simon Fraser University, I gained experience with helping students with these and various other technological challenges.

In addition I have enjoyed creating a variety of websites for artists and art projects. You can see a selection at casperleerink.com/code

Work Experience

Freelance Web Developer

Casper Leerink - Web Design and Development - Vancouver, BC September 2018 to Present

As an independent web developer, I created portfolio websites for artists as well as web apps for art projects such as a custom map or an interactive canvas application.

Teaching Assistant

Simon Fraser University - School for the Contemporary Arts - Vancouver, BC September 2018 to April 2021

A part-time job that includes teaching, grading and 1 on 1 consultation with bachelor students in the fields of music theory, music history and sound.

Digital Media Facilitator

Simon Fraser University - Library - Burnaby, BC January 2020 to June 2020

Creating tutorials and helping student with using the maker space in the library including audio, video and virtual reality software, 3D Printing and Laser Cutting.

Education

Master's Degree in Fine Arts

Simon Fraser University - Vancouver, BC September 2018 to December 2020

Bachelor's Degree in Music Performance

ArtEZ University of the Arts - Zwolle, The Netherlands September 2013 to July 2017

Skills

- HTML5 (3 years)
- CSS (3 years)
- JavaScript/ES6 (3 years)
- React (2 years)
- Adobe Suite (XD, Illustrator, Premiere) (1 year)
- Teaching
- Arduino (1 year)
- Web Development (3 years)
- Git
- GitHub
- Node.js
- Media and Communication

Languages

- English Fluent
- Dutch Fluent

Links

https://casperleerink.com/

https://casperleerink.com/code

https://github.com/casperleerink